ok that was just amazing his story
always gives me children well now it is
a brilliant doctor genius allergic but
before we do that we have to ask the
Consul General ursula kocher to come up
so that she can actually do the IMP
introduction she's the daughter of
polar's other grades she were a great
friend is a graduate of the University
of Akron and has a degree in philosophy
politics and economics in 1991 she moved
to prompt regretted to Poland in 2005
she was elected to the polar Senate was
an active member of the committee for
integration appearance and content to
impulsive rock and other day in 2007 she
became a member of a european parliament
between februari 2011 in November 2014
she acted as ambassador and permanent
work representative of the Republic of
Poland to the council of europe in
transit in the summer of two thousand
fourteen she took the post their pullins
council general in New York and this is
her very first visit to clarence oh
we're very happy to have her and she
will be in nothing
you